<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<schedule>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:00:00</time>
      <type>story</type>
      <user>Justin's Stormtracker Forecast</user>
      <message>Today is another "warmer than normal" day with highs near 80 degrees...</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/Justin_Stormtracker.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body>
      <title>Justin's Stormtracker Forecast</title>
      <description>Today is another "warmer than normal" day with highs near 80 degrees...</description>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/content/forecast.jpg</image>
      <link>http://www.wkrn.com/story/17349186/crews-respond-to-downtown-church-fire</link>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[
Cool weather is in the works this week, but today looks mild. Expect a mostly sunny sky and afternoon highs in the lower 70s. A northwest breeze kicks in today and will gust to 20 mph from time to time.

Overnight lows drop to the lower 40s with partly cloudy sky.

Tuesday features a steady northwest breeze and highs in the middle 60s.

We'll watch for patchy frost on Tuesday night (and Wednesday night) as lows drop to the middle 30s in Nashville and possibly lower 30s to the north and east. Highs Wednesday may only approach the upper 50s, despite some sunshine!

We'll rebound through the 60s into the 70s between Thursday and Friday afternoons.
        ]]>
      </text>
    </body>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:00:07</time>
      <type>comment</type>
      <user>Christine Diez</user>
      <message>80 degrees in march. Not looking forward to July! #TOOHOT</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/christine_diez.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body/>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:00:14</time>
      <type>comment</type>
      <user>Mr Lova Lova</user>
      <message>I'll worry about July when it comes @ChristineDiez. Lovin' this March weather! #JUSTRIGHT</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/mr_lova_lova.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body/>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:00:19</time>
      <type>info</type>
      <user>Coming Up</user>
      <message>Google trying to be like Amazon. We'll tell you how in the next 30 minutes.</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/wkrn.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body>
      <title>Coming Up</title>
      <description>Google trying to be like Amazon. We'll tell you how in the next 30 minutes.</description>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/content/coming_up.jpg</image>
      <link>http://www.wkrn.com/</link>
    </body>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:00:23</time>
      <type>info</type>
      <user>Coming Up</user>
      <message>Local family adopts four children from China who needed something a little extra special. That story is up next.</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/wkrn.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body>
      <title>Coming Up</title>
      <description>Local family adopts four children from China who needed something a little extra special. That story is up next.</description>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/content/coming_up.jpg</image>
      <link>http://www.wkrn.com/</link>
    </body>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:00:34</time>
      <type>info</type>
      <user>Pool &amp; Spa Depot</user>
      <message>Largest Selection in Tennessee. Nashville, Cookville, Bowling Green Locations. Call us @ 351-8000</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/pool_spa_depot.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body>
      <title>Pool &amp; Spa Depot</title>
      <description>Largest Selection in Tennessee. Nashville, Cookville, Bowling Green Locations. Call us @ 351-8000</description>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/content/pool_spa.jpg</image>
      <link>http://poolandspadepot.com</link>
    </body>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:00:41</time>
      <type>comment</type>
      <user>Liam McDonald</user>
      <message>We got our pool here last summer and we've haven't had a problem since.</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/liam_mcdonald.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body/>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:00:50</time>
      <type>info</type>
      <user>Nashville Nissan</user>
      <message>It's our annual Nashville Nissan Now Sales Event!</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/nashville_nissan.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body>
      <title>Nashville Nissan</title>
      <description>It's our annual Nashville Nissan Now Sales Event!</description>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/content/nashville_nissan.jpg</image>
      <link>http://nashvillenissan.com</link>
    </body>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:00:57</time>
      <type>story</type>
      <user>WKRN News</user>
      <message>Fire damages downtown church recreation center. Read the story.</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/wkrn_news.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body>
      <title>Fire damages downtown church recreation center</title>
      <description>Thirty-five teenagers are safe after fire erupted at a downtown Nashville church recreation center early Friday morning.</description>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/content/church_fire.jpg</image>
      <link>http://www.wkrn.com/story/17349186/crews-respond-to-downtown-church-fire</link>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[
NASHVILLE, Tenn. - Three dozen teenagers are safe after fire erupted at a downtown Nashville church recreation center early Friday morning.

The call went out just after 5 a.m. at the First Baptist Church located at 108 7th Avenue South.

Smoke could be seen coming from the structure.

"The smoke filled the gym almost immediately. By the time we got everybody out, you couldn't even move, [it was] just thick black smoke," Youth Pastor Quillian Mercer said. 

The teens staying at the church's recreation center are from Atlanta and are in Music City working with the Nashville Rescue Mission while on spring break.  

Crews were able to contain most of the damage to the kitchen area.

"One of our men were sleeping in the gym area and heard a tapping sound. [He] thought someone was in the kitchen, stood up and looked through. When he looked through, he saw fire in the kitchen and immediately started getting people," Mercer said. 

He continued, "He got the boys out of the gym immediately, came upstairs where the rest of us were and just screaming, ‘Fire!' and we were able to get out the emergency exits pretty quickly." 

Investigators are working to determine what sparked the blaze.

"We actually had time last night to share what God had done through our time, and just had an amazing time. This is just going to be the exclamation point, I guess," Mercer said. 

No one was injured.
        ]]>
      </text>
    </body>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:01:05</time>
      <type>info</type>
      <user>Nashville Nissan</user>
      <message>Lock in internet pricing now!</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/nashville_nissan.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body>
      <title>Nashville Nissan</title>
      <description>Lock in internet pricing now!</description>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/content/nashville_nissan_1.jpg</image>
      <link>http://www.candsleads.com/1stc/DowntownNashvilleNissan/index.html</link>
    </body>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:1:12</time>
      <type>story</type>
      <user>WKRN News</user>
      <message>Mother charged with DUI, neglect after losing 5-year-old. Read the story</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/wkrn_news.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body>
      <title>Mother charged with DUI, neglect after losing 5-year-old</title>
      <description>A 21-year-old Clarksville mother was arrested early Friday morning after losing her five-year-old child.</description>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/content/mother.jpg</image>
      <link>http://www.wkrn.com/story/17350996/mother-charged-with-dui-neglect-after-losing-5-year-old</link>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[
CLARKSVILLE, Tenn. - A 21-year-old Clarksville mother was arrested early Friday morning after losing her five-year-old child.

Police said Reagan Martin was pulled over shortly after Midnight on Ft. Campbell Boulevard at Airport Road after an officer noticed her vehicle swerving and traveling erratically.

"The driving was so bad the vehicle was going into oncoming lanes of traffic. The officer initiated the traffic stop, made contact, the driver's speech was very slurred, almost incoherent," explained Clarksville police spokesperson Jim Knoll. 

Authorities said backup officers arrived on the scene and recognized Martin from a traffic crash earlier in the evening in which Martin rear-ended another vehicle.

Officer Chris MacMillan had worked the earlier crash and also recalled that there were two children, a male and female, in the vehicle with Martin.

In the later stop only a two-year-old boy was present, police said.

Officers asked Martin where the female child was and she replied that she didn't know.

"She gave four locations where her kid could be and it was all over the city. We put the word out, we have a child lost on their own. We checked her license, they went to that address [on Walnut Street], the door is unlocked, there is a five-year-old girl alone and scared," Knoll said. 

He continued, "She said her mom left and she went to sleep, she was very scared. That officer on scene cooked her ravioli till father could be contacted."

According to the police, Martin told officers that she had taken medication that is commonly used to treat seizures and panic attacks

Nashville's News 2 Investigates spoke with Martin's husband of two years, Markellis about the incident. 

Markellis Martin said his wife is a good person and mother who made a mistake. 

"I talked to her today and she doesn't remember driving or anything happened. She is a terrific mom, she is great with the kids, and she is incredible, people have their flaws unfortunately hers, she has to take medication for hers, and the side effects sometimes cause nasty results," he said, adding, " I hope everyone doesn't see her as a bad mom that is something she isn't. People make mistakes. I am going to stand behind her like a husband should and we will push through this." 

Reagan Martin is charged with child abuse and neglect, driving under the influence and reckless endangerment.

She was booked into the Montgomery County jail on a $75,500 bond.

Both children were turned over to their father and the Department of Children's Services has been notified of the incident. 

Martin did not have a previous arrest history. 

She celebrated her 21st birthday less than a month ago.
        ]]>
      </text>
    </body>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:01:19</time>
      <type>info</type>
      <user>Sprintz</user>
      <message>One of the biggest Sprintz Warehouse Clearance Sales ever!</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/sprintz.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body>
      <title>Sprintz</title>
      <description>One of the biggest Sprintz Warehouse Clearance Sales ever!</description>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/content/sprintz.jpg</image>
      <link>http://www.candsleads.com/1stc/DowntownNashvilleNissan/index.html</link>
    </body>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:01:26</time>
      <type>comment</type>
      <user>James Tomilson</user>
      <message>Can't wait to see what the deal is with the adoption family!</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/james_tomilson.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body/>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:01:32</time>
      <type>coupon</type>
      <user>Sprintz</user>
      <message>Use this coupon to save an additonal 10% on any Sealy mattress</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/sprintz.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body>
      <store>Sprintz</store>
      <coupon>Save 10% on purchase of any Sealy mattress</coupon>
      <code>SPRINTZ201</code>
      <link>http://www.sprintz.com</link>
    </body>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:1:40</time>
      <type>story</type>
      <user>WKRN News</user>
      <message>Family of pedestrian struck by alleged drunk driver files lawsuit. Read the story</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/wkrn_news.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body>
      <title>Family of pedestrian struck by alleged drunk driver files lawsuit</title>
      <description>The family of one of the young men who died after he was struck by an alleged drunk driver on Demonbruen Street last December has filed a wrongful death suit.</description>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/content/pedestrian.jpg</image>
      <link>http://www.wkrn.com/story/17350550/family-of-pedestrian-struck-by-alleged-drunk-driver-files-lawsuit</link>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[
NASHVILLE, Tenn. - The family of one of the young men who died after he was struck by an alleged drunk driver on Demonbreun Street last December has filed a wrongful death suit against the driver, his passenger and the company who hosted the holiday party the pair attended earlier in the night.

Trevor Bradshaw was behind the wheel of the SUV that hit Michael Brooksher and Tommy Allen as they crossed Demonbreun Street in the early morning hours of December 10.

He is charged with vehicular homicide.

Bradshaw's girlfriend and front seat passenger Erin Brown is also charged because police said she gave Bradshaw the keys to her SUV even though she knew he was drunk.

"She knew he'd been drinking," Metro police Det. Jessie Loy testified in February. "She gave him the keys anyway. She provided Mr. Bradshaw with a means to operate the vehicle."

The complaint, filed by Allen's mother, Lela Ann McKee, alleges Bradshaw and Brown got drunk at a party hosted by Nashville printing company Jive Printing.

The suit says free alcohol was served at the "Naughty and Nice" event.

"They had one vehicle to give rides to people that may have had too many to drink at a party where there were hundreds of people attending," McKee's attorney, Matt Hardin told Nashville's News 2. 

Metro Government is also named in the lawsuit, which seeks a total of $15 million in damages.

"His mother wants justice in this case for her son which is the only avenue she has left," said Hardin.

The 23-year-old Allen passed away from injuries sustained in the crash in early February.  

Brooksher, 22, died December 12.
        ]]>
      </text>
    </body>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:01:49</time>
      <type>info</type>
      <user>Nissan</user>
      <message>People everywhere are dropping everything to get to the Nissan Now Sales Event!</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/nissan.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body>
      <title>Nissan</title>
      <description>People everywhere are dropping everything to get to the Nissan Now Sales Event!</description>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/content/nissan_now.jpg</image>
      <link>http://choosenissan.com</link>
    </body>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:01:59</time>
      <type>comment</type>
      <user>Tori</user>
      <message>Has anybody out there ever dropped their coffee becasue of a car commercial? #YEAHRIGHT</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/tori.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body/>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:02:08</time>
      <type>info</type>
      <user>Nissan</user>
      <message>Go to ChooseNissan.com now!</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/nissan.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body>
      <title>Nissan</title>
      <description>Go to ChooseNissan.com now!</description>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/content/nissan_now_1.jpg</image>
      <link>http://choosenissan.com</link>
    </body>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:02:19</time>
      <type>info</type>
      <user>SafeLink.com</user>
      <message>If you have an emergency outside the home how do you call for help?</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/safelink.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body>
      <title>SafeLink.com</title>
      <description>If you have an emergency outside the home how do you call for help?</description>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/content/safelink.jpg</image>
      <link>http://safelink.com</link>
    </body>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:02:34</time>
      <type>coupon</type>
      <user>SafeLink.com</user>
      <message>Use this coupon for an additional free phone for a family member</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/safelink.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body>
      <store>SafeLink.com</store>
      <coupon>Free phone for a family member</coupon>
      <code>SAFEFAMPHONE</code>
      <link>http://www.safelink.com</link>
    </body>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:2:43</time>
      <type>story</type>
      <user>WKRN News</user>
      <message>New Nashville billboard gives face to atheism. Read the story</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/wkrn_news.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body>
      <title>New Nashville billboard gives face to atheism</title>
      <description>Freedom from Religion Foundation's hot pink billboard placed along I-40 features a photograph of a young woman with the words...</description>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/content/atheist.jpg</image>
      <link>http://www.wkrn.com/story/17347806/new-nashville-billboard-gives-face-to-atheism</link>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[
NASHVILLE, Tenn. - A non-profit organization's newest billboard is attracting the attention of Nashville drivers. 

Freedom from Religion Foundation's hot pink billboard placed along Interstate 40 West, just west of downtown, features a photograph of a young woman named Grace with the words, "This is what an atheist looks like."

The 23-year-old college student told Nashville's News 2 she was raised Catholic, but abandoned those views in her late teens. 

"I think people sometimes have a misconception. I think they think we're all unhappy, dark people, some people just don't understand how someone can live a fulfilled life without believing in God," she explained.

Grace moved to Clarksville three years ago from Houston with her husband, who is also an atheist and a soldier at Ft. Campbell.

"We're soldiers. We're doctors. We just happen to not follow religion," Grace said.

She told Nashville's News 2 she hopes being out as an atheist in the so-called "Bible Belt" will help change negative perceptions of her views and start a conversation.

"I hope it starts a dialogue between the religious and non-religious community because we need to understand each other to respect each other," she said.

Grace continued, "I just believe I have one life to live and I'm going to be good throughout it not because I'm afraid of being damned or because I want to be rewarded in an after life.  I just want to be a good person because it's the right thing to do."

The billboard is the first of its kind in Nashville.  The Freedom from Religion Foundation said they plan to launch a multi-city campaign in upcoming months.
        ]]>
      </text>
    </body>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:02:49</time>
      <type>info</type>
      <user>Beaman Buick GMC</user>
      <message>Hail Damage Mega Sale! Choose from over 400 units. But when they're gone, they're gone!</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/beaman.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body>
      <title>Beaman Buick GMC</title>
      <description>Hail Damage Mega Sale! Choose from over 400 units. But when they're gone, they're gone!</description>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/content/beaman_hail.jpg</image>
      <link>http://www.beamanbuickgmc.com/</link>
    </body>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:02:57</time>
      <type>comment</type>
      <user>Andy Cordan</user>
      <message>I dropped my coffee in my lap on the way to work this morning? Does that count @Tori?</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/andy_cordan.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body/>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:03:10</time>
      <type>coupon</type>
      <user>Beaman Buick GMC</user>
      <message>First customer that says wkrn hail get $500 off instantly!</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/beaman.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body>
      <body>
        <store>Beaman Buick GMC</store>
        <coupon>First customer that says wkrn hail get $500 off instantly!</coupon>
        <code>BBGMC99</code>
        <link>http://www.beamanbuickgmc.com/</link>
      </body>
    </body>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:03:19</time>
      <type>info</type>
      <user>Pool &amp; Spa Depot</user>
      <message>Largest Selection in Tennessee. Nashville, Cookville, Bowling Green Locations. Call us @ 351-8000</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/pool_spa_depot.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body>
      <title>Pool &amp; Spa Depot</title>
      <description>Largest Selection in Tennessee. Nashville, Cookville, Bowling Green Locations. Call us @ 351-8000</description>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/content/pool_spa.jpg</image>
      <link>http://poolandspadepot.com</link>
    </body>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:03:28</time>
      <type>comment</type>
      <user>Liam McDonald</user>
      <message>Got ours at the Cookville location and the staff is great!</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/liam_mcdonald.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body/>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:03:39</time>
      <type>info</type>
      <user>News 2</user>
      <message>Visit the waiting child website and see how you can help a child.</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/wkrn.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body>
      <title>News 2</title>
      <description>Visit the Waiting Child website</description>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/content/waiting_child.jpg</image>
      <link>http://www.afamilyforeverychild.org/kids/All_Kids.php</link>
    </body>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:03:50</time>
      <type>poll</type>
      <user>Let Us Know What You Think</user>
      <message>Would you adopt a child with a heart condition?</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/poll.png</image>
    </header>
    <body>
      <question text="Would you adopt a child with a heart condition?" votes="100" />
      <response text="Yes" votes="76" />
      <response text="No" votes="24" />
    </body>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:03:56</time>
      <type>info</type>
      <user>News 2</user>
      <message>Meet the Irwins!</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/wkrn.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body>
      <title>News 2</title>
      <description>Meet the Irwins!</description>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/content/irwins_meet.jpg</image>
      <link>http://www.afamilyforeverychild.org/kids/All_Kids.php</link>
    </body>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:04:02</time>
      <type>info</type>
      <user>News 2</user>
      <message>Over a thousand children were adopted in Middle Tennessee last year.</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/wkrn.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body>
      <title>News 2</title>
      <description>Over a thousand children were adopted in Middle Tennessee last year.</description>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/content/nashville_adoption.jpg</image>
      <link>http://www.afamilyforeverychild.org/kids/All_Kids.php</link>
    </body>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:04:12</time>
      <type>poll</type>
      <user>Let Us Know What You Think</user>
      <message>Is Middle Tennessee a good place to raise an adopted child?</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/poll.png</image>
    </header>
    <body>
      <question text="Is Middle Tennessee a good place to raise an adopted child?" votes="100" />
      <response text="Yes" votes="76" />
      <response text="No" votes="24" />
    </body>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:04:16</time>
      <type>info</type>
      <user>News 2</user>
      <message>4 of the 6 children are from the Waiting Child program in China.</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/wkrn.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body>
      <title>News 2</title>
      <description>Visit the Waiting Child website</description>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/content/waiting_child.jpg</image>
      <link>http://www.afamilyforeverychild.org/kids/All_Kids.php</link>
    </body>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:04:22</time>
      <type>comment</type>
      <user>TPBGirl2011</user>
      <message>Amazing people and an amazing family! #UNCONDITIONALLOVE</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/TPBGirl2011.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body/>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:04:30</time>
      <type>info</type>
      <user>News 2</user>
      <message>Each family gets matched to a specific child with a specfic need.</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/wkrn.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body>
      <title>News 2</title>
      <description>Visit the Waiting Child website</description>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/content/nashville_adoption.jpg</image>
      <link>http://www.afamilyforeverychild.org/kids/All_Kids.php</link>
    </body>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:04:36</time>
      <type>comment</type>
      <user>AGopal16</user>
      <message>And I thought my day was a challenge. Stories like this really put everything in perspective.</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/agopal16.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body/>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:04:45</time>
      <type>comment</type>
      <user>Sophie Tucker</user>
      <message>You guys should also check out adoptuskids if you want to change somebodys life.</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/sophietucker.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body/>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:04:53</time>
      <type>comment</type>
      <user>TonyKemp6</user>
      <message>Do you think you could do what they do @TPBGirl2011? #NASHVILLECARES</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/TonyKemp6.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body/>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:05:05</time>
      <type>info</type>
      <user>News 2</user>
      <message>A family trip to China earlier this year brought back their youngest, Sally.</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/wkrn.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body>
      <title>News 2</title>
      <description>A family trip to China earlier this year brought back their youngest, Sally.</description>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/content/irwins_china.jpg</image>
      <link>http://www.afamilyforeverychild.org/kids/All_Kids.php</link>
    </body>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:05:15</time>
      <type>comment</type>
      <user>Amanda Murphy</user>
      <message>Beautiful Story. Beautiful family.</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/amanda_murphy.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body/>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:05:29</time>
      <type>info</type>
      <user>News 2</user>
      <message>The Irwin Family...perhaps to be continued.</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/wkrn.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body>
      <title>News 2</title>
      <description>To Be Continued!</description>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/content/irwins_meet.jpg</image>
      <link>http://www.afamilyforeverychild.org/kids/All_Kids.php</link>
    </body>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:5:39</time>
      <type>info</type>
      <user>News 2</user>
      <message>Register for the American Heart Association heart walk this fall.</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/wkrn.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body>
      <title>Heart Walk</title>
      <description>Register for the American Heart Association heart walk this fall.</description>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/content/heart_walk.jpg</image>
      <link>http://www.heartwalk.org/site/c.rjJ0J6MHIoE/b.5777283/k.2284/Heart_Walk__National_Web_Site.htm</link>
    </body>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:05:51</time>
      <type>info</type>
      <user>News 2</user>
      <message>Happy 100th Birthday Lynwood Leach!</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/wkrn.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body>
      <title>Birthdays</title>
      <description>Happy 100th Birthday Lynwood Leach!</description>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/content/100yearold.png</image>
      <link>http://prod.bti.tv/media/content/100yearold.png</link>
    </body>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:06:02</time>
      <type>comment</type>
      <user>Scruffy Zack</user>
      <message>Hope i still look that good @ 100!</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/scruffyzack.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body/>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:06:11</time>
      <type>comment</type>
      <user>Natalie Davis</user>
      <message>Happy 100th Lynwood!</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/natalie_davis.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body/>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:06:21</time>
      <type>info</type>
      <user>Coming Up</user>
      <message>Predators clinch a playoff spot. We'll tell you how you can show your support.</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/wkrn.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body>
      <title>Coming Up</title>
      <description>Predators clinch a playoff spot. We'll tell you how you can show your support.</description>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/content/coming_up.jpg</image>
      <link>http://www.wkrn.com/</link>
    </body>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:6:29</time>
      <type>story</type>
      <user>WKRN Sports</user>
      <message>Predators eliminate Stars with 2-0 victory. Read the story.</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/wkrn_sports.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body>
      <title>Predators eliminate Stars with 2-0 victory</title>
      <description>Pekka Rinne made 28 saves for his fifth shutout of the season, Francis Bouillon scored at 4:28 of the third period, and the Nashville Predators beat the Dallas Stars 2-0 on Thursday night.</description>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/content/predators.jpg</image>
      <link>http://www.wkrn.com/story/17348013/predators-eliminate-stars-with-2-0-victory</link>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[
NASHVILLE, Tenn. (AP) - Pekka Rinne made 28 saves for his fifth shutout of the season, Francis Bouillon scored at 4:28 of the third period, and the Nashville Predators beat the Dallas Stars 2-0 on Thursday night to grab back control of their playoff slot with their third win in four games.

With the win and Detroit losing 2-1 to New Jersey, Nashville moved back into fourth in the Western Conference, a point a head of the Red Wings. Now the Predators need only wrap up the regular season Saturday night at Colorado with a win to start the playoffs at home and finish ahead of Detroit for the first time in franchise history.

Patric Hornqvist had an assist and clinched the win with a goal with 2 minutes left.

The Stars lost their fourth straight in being eliminated. The Stars came in ninth and needed at least a point, but the loss allowed Los Angeles and Phoenix to clinch berths and put San Jose on the verge.
        ]]>
      </text>
    </body>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:06:34</time>
      <type>info</type>
      <user>Honda</user>
      <message>Honda Civic is the best selling small car in america.</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/honda.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body>
      <title>Honda</title>
      <description>The best selling small car in america!</description>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/content/honda_civic.jpg</image>
      <link>http://www.honda.com/</link>
    </body>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:06:43</time>
      <type>comment</type>
      <user>Dalila Thomas</user>
      <message>I have a honda and i love it!</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/dalila_thomas.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body/>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:06:49</time>
      <type>info</type>
      <user>Honda</user>
      <message>0.9 % APR on select vehicles. Visit your local Honda dealer for the Really Big Sales Event.</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/honda.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body>
      <title>Honda</title>
      <description>0.9 % APR on select vehicles!</description>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/content/honda_civic_1.jpg</image>
      <link>http://www.honda.com/</link>
    </body>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:06:55</time>
      <type>story</type>
      <user>WKRN News</user>
      <message>Woman with autism builds business to help others with similar disorders. Read the story.</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/wkrn_news.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body>
      <title>Woman with autism builds business to help others with similar disorders</title>
      <description>A Franklin woman who was diagnosed with a form of autism at the age of 38 has built a business to help others with similar disabilities.</description>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/content/autism.jpg</image>
      <link>http://www.wkrn.com/story/17345124/woman-with-autism-builds-business-to-help-others-with-similar-disorders</link>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[
FRANKLIN, Tenn. - A Franklin woman who was diagnosed with a form of autism at the age of 38 has built a business to help others with similar disabilities. 

"I tell people being autistic never disabled me, but trying to be normal nearly killed me," Dena Gassner told Nashville's News 2.

Gassner said after she was diagnosed with the disorder she decided to open a business that would help others affected by autism. 

"I was diagnosed with Asperger's at 38 and at that time there were no support and services to help people take the diagnosis off of the paper and apply in real time in how you experience it every single day," she explained. 

Gassner's business, the Center for Understanding, offers coaching and counseling to help adults with autism better manage the highly variable developmental disorder and integrate into society. 

"A lot of our people come in very shame ridden. They don't want anyone to know. They spend time in this atmosphere of authenticity and go, ‘Wow it's not so bad after all,'" she said. 

According to the latest report from the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, one in 88 children is diagnosed with autism. 

The report states this number has increased by 78% in the past six years and 1,000% in reported prevalence over the past 40 years. 

Gassner said despite the increase, she still believes those numbers are low. 

"We're massively under estimating the number of adults," she said. 

Despite inspiring other adults who suffer from autism, Gassner said she does not see herself as a role model. 

"I see myself as a person who hasn't achieved her personal best. I keep pressing forward. I [am] just really committed to what I'm doing here and just hoping that we can continue to sustain it," she explained. 

Gassner said her son, who is now 22-years-old, was diagnosed with autism when he was a child. 

For more information on the Center for Understanding, visit centerforunderstanding.net. 

Click here to read the latest autism report released by the CDC. 
        ]]>
      </text>
    </body>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:07:05</time>
      <type>info</type>
      <user>Vanderbilt Childrens Hospital</user>
      <message>Whatever your child needs to get well, you'll find it here.</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/vanderbilt.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body>
      <title>Vanderbilt Childrens Hospital</title>
      <description>Whatever your child needs to get well, you'll find it here.</description>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/content/vanderbilt_staircase.jpg</image>
      <link>http://www.childrenshospital.vanderbilt.org/</link>
    </body>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:07:12</time>
      <type>comment</type>
      <user>Dean Santillan</user>
      <message>Go Preds!</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/dean_santillan.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body/>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:07:20</time>
      <type>info</type>
      <user>Vanderbilt Childrens Hospital</user>
      <message>Your childs very own hospital.</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/vanderbilt.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body>
      <title>Vanderbilt Childrens Hospital</title>
      <description>Your childs very own hospital.</description>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/content/vanderbilt_child.jpg</image>
      <link>http://www.childrenshospital.vanderbilt.org/</link>
    </body>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:07:27</time>
      <type>story</type>
      <user>WKRN News</user>
      <message>Thieves steal lawn equipment from Murfreesboro church. Read the story.</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/wkrn_news.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body>
      <title>Thieves steal lawn equipment from Murfreesboro church</title>
      <description>Thieves burglarized a Rutherford County church earlier this week, stealing hundreds of dollars worth of lawn equipment.</description>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/content/church_lawn.jpg</image>
      <link>http://www.wkrn.com/story/17346572/thieves-steal-lawn-equipment-from-murfreesboro-church</link>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[
MURFREESBORO, Tenn. - Thieves burglarized a Rutherford County church earlier this week, stealing hundreds of dollars worth of lawn equipment. 

Pastor Dorsey Robinson of Jesus Oasis Independent Church discovered Wednesday that thieves had broken into a tool shed connected to the church and made off with $600 worth of tools.

"There was a lawnmower, three weed eaters and a cooker," he told Nashville's News 2.

According to Robinson, Murfreesboro police said they could not devote an investigative team to find the culprits, but that they will notify area pawnshops of the stolen items. 

"If those items shows up in there, then the pawn shop will in turn get in touch with them, then they would get in touch with us," Robinson explained. 

Robinson told Nashville's News 2 he is not as concerned about the missing items as he is the suspect or suspects who stole them. 

"It just shows you a condition and it's my prayer that whoever might have done this might, that the Lord might touch their heart. And perhaps they will have a desire to bring it back," he said. 

Anyone with information on the incident is urged to contact Murfreesboro police at 615- 849-2670.
        ]]>
      </text>
    </body>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:07:34</time>
      <type>info</type>
      <user>Darrell Waltrip Subara</user>
      <message>Come celebrate the Subara Love Spring Sales Event.</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/waltrip.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body>
      <title>Darrell Waltrip Subara</title>
      <description>Come celebrate the Subara Love Spring Sales Event.</description>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/content/subaru_spring.jpg</image>
      <link>http://www.darrellwaltripsubaru.com</link>
    </body>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:07:41</time>
      <type>comment</type>
      <user>Chris Gary</user>
      <message>The best driver ever and the best person to buy a car off ever!</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/chris_gary.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body/>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:07:49</time>
      <type>coupon</type>
      <user>Darrell Waltrip Subaru</user>
      <message>First 5 customers that mention this ad save $1000 instantly</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/waltrip.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body>
      <store>Darrell Waltrip Subaru</store>
      <coupon>First 5 customers that mention this ad save $1000 instantly</coupon>
      <code>DW1000</code>
      <link>http://www.darrellwaltripsubaru.com</link>
    </body>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:07:55</time>
      <type>story</type>
      <user>WKRN News</user>
      <message>Anonymous letter prompts legal battle at private school. Read the story.</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/wkrn_news.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body>
      <title>Anonymous letter prompts legal battle at private school</title>
      <description>The battle involving Currey Ingram Academy in Brentwood began when an anonymous letter was sent to parents earlier this year.</description>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/content/letter.jpg</image>
      <link>http://www.wkrn.com/story/17345777/anonymous-letter-prompts-legal-battle-at-private-school</link>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[
BRENTWOOD, Tenn. - Legal findings involving former parents and a teacher at Currey Ingram Academy in Brentwood are escalating after an anonymous letter was sent to parents of the school criticizing Headmistress Kathy Rayburn and alleging lack of transparency as a non-profit. 

For 10 years Sheila Wysocki's child attended Currey Ingram Academy, a college preparatory school that offers individualized education for students with learning disabilities. 

According to Wysocki, she was served with a subpoena following a parent-teacher conference last month. 

"I walked out with my son on school property and a board member who is an attorney serves me a subpoena on property," she told Nashville's News 2.

Immediately following the incident she said removed her child from the school.

"They could have just said, 'We need to talk to you,'" Wysocki said, continuing, "Instead they serve me a subpoena and later I found out it was because I was raising money for a teacher who's being sued."

The teacher Wysocki was helping raise money for, James Warbel resigned from his position in February.

According to school officials, Warbel spoke about the academy to students in a negative light. 

"We had reason to believe that he had intended to continue those types of conversations and it was a breach of his contract to contact students, so we felt we had to enforce that provision for that reason," Currey Ingram Board President Miller Hogan explained.

Since the incident, the school has issued a restraining order against Warbel. 

Nashville's News 2 spoke with his attorney, Mark Freeman, who said he believes the retraining order is a form of bullying in an attempt to reveal the authors of the anonymous letter. 

"I think at this point they know he didn't write it because he's testified under oath that he didn't write it, but they want him to implicate others who may have written it," Freeman explained. 

Hogan responded to the bullying allegations by saying, "Availing yourself of legal remedies that you have, I don't understand how that can be bullying." 

The anonymous letter also went on to criticize the way Headmistress Rayburn handled the employment of her son at the school. 

Rayburn's son E.B. pled guilty earlier this year to statutory rape charges involving a 16-year-old boy. The victim was not a student at the school. 

E.B. who is now a registered sex offender has since been placed on administrative leave following his 2011 arrest. 

"We immediately communicated to parents after that decision.  I've never received a complaint from a parent, a teacher or administrator, a student or authorities that would raise any type of concern in that regard," Hogan said. 

Since Nashville's News 2's interview with Wysocki, the school has issued a court order to have her part of a restraining order.
        ]]>
      </text>
    </body>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:08:05</time>
      <type>story</type>
      <user>WKRN News</user>
      <message>MegaMillions Record Jackpot. Read the story</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/wkrn.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body>
      <title>Odds of winning record Mega Millions jackpot 1 in 176 million</title>
      <description>A world-record $540 million Mega Millions jackpot has lottery players lining up for tickets early Friday in hopes of becoming an overnight multimillionaire.</description>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/content/lottery.jpg</image>
      <link>http://www.wkrn.com/story/17293727/mega-millions-world-record-jackpot</link>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[
ATLANTA (AP) - The drawing for what could be the single biggest lottery payout the world has ever seen is finally here.

The numbers drawn Friday night in Atlanta were 2-4-23-38-46, Mega Ball 23.

A $640 million jackpot is up for grabs. Taken as a lump sum, it would amount to $462 million -- or about $347 million after federal tax withholding. It will be a couple of hours for details on
possible winners come out.

Across the country, Americans plunked down an estimated $1.5 billion on the longest of long shots: 1 in 176 million. 

The rarity of Friday's jackpot was fueling the fervor. Lines formed at grocery stores, gas stations, liquor stops and other venues across the country.
        ]]>
      </text>
    </body>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:08:13</time>
      <type>info</type>
      <user>Coming Up</user>
      <message>A Truck Driver tries to beat a train and ends up in a crash</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/wkrn.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body>
      <title>Coming Up</title>
      <description>A Truck Driver tries to beat a train and ends up in a crash</description>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/content/coming_up.jpg</image>
      <link>http://www.wkrn.com/</link>
    </body>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:08:20</time>
      <type>info</type>
      <user>Coming Up</user>
      <message>Preds are in the playoffs and trying to start a new trend today</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/wkrn.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body>
      <title>Coming Up</title>
      <description>Preds are in the playoffs and trying to start a new trend today</description>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/content/coming_up.jpg</image>
      <link>http://www.wkrn.com/</link>
    </body>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:08:28</time>
      <type>info</type>
      <user>Take a Picture</user>
      <message>Do It! Take a picture and post it on our Facebook page! We'll tell you more in a moment.</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/wkrn.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body>
      <title>Take a picture!</title>
      <description>Do It! Take a picture and post it on our Facebook page! We'll tell you more in a moment.</description>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/content/coming_up.jpg</image>
      <link>http://www.wkrn.com/</link>
    </body>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:08:35</time>
      <type>comment</type>
      <user>Shelbot</user>
      <message>Does anybody else think the lottery is a tax against people who can't do math? #LOTTERYBITES</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/shelbot.png</image>
    </header>
    <body/>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:08:42</time>
      <type>comment</type>
      <user>Genaro Maldonado</user>
      <message>As long as it keeps my taxes down i don't mind they play @Shelbot</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/genaro_maldonado.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body/>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:08:50</time>
      <type>story</type>
      <user>Justin's Stormtracker Forecast</user>
      <message>Today is another "warmer than normal" day with highs near 80 degrees...</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/Justin_Stormtracker.jpg</image>
    </header>
    <body>
      <title>Justin's Stormtracker Forecast</title>
      <description>Today is another "warmer than normal" day with highs near 80 degrees...</description>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/content/forecast.jpg</image>
      <link>http://www.wkrn.com/story/17349186/crews-respond-to-downtown-church-fire</link>
      <text>
        <![CDATA[
Cool weather is in the works this week, but today looks mild. Expect a mostly sunny sky and afternoon highs in the lower 70s. A northwest breeze kicks in today and will gust to 20 mph from time to time.
 
Overnight lows drop to the lower 40s with partly cloudy sky.
 
Tuesday features a steady northwest breeze and highs in the middle 60s.
 
We'll watch for patchy frost on Tuesday night (and Wednesday night) as lows drop to the middle 30s in Nashville and possibly lower 30s to the north and east. Highs Wednesday may only approach the upper 50s, despite some sunshine!
 
We'll rebound through the 60s into the 70s between Thursday and Friday afternoons.
        ]]>
      </text>
    </body>
  </event>
  <event>
    <header>
      <time>00:09:02</time>
      <type>poll</type>
      <user>Let Us Know What You Think</user>
      <message>Have you been enjoying these warmer than usual days?</message>
      <image>http://prod.bti.tv/media/users/poll.png</image>
    </header>
    <body>
      <question text="Have you been enjoying these warmer than usual days?" votes="100" />
      <response text="Yes - Warm days are my friend!" votes="76" />
      <response text="No - My allergies are killing me!" votes="24" />
    </body>
  </event>
</schedule>